

Name: Ana Antunes Position: HR | Recruiter

Languages: Português (Native or Bilingual), English (Full Professional), Espanhol (Professional Working)

Location: Lisbon, Portugal

Phone: Email: Whatsapp: Best Reached:

Start:

Holidays Booked:

Ana is a psychologist turned Talent Acquisition Specialist, expertly blending behavioural science with recruitment strategy. She helps companies find not just talent, but the right people, through thoughtful sourcing, structured interviews, and personality-based assessment. Ana is experienced with platforms like Salesforce, SAP SuccessFactors, and LinkedIn Recruiter, and possesses strong skills in employer branding, onboarding, team coordination, and administrative support, both in-person and remotely. With certifications in SHL and OPP, and a foundation in clinical psychology, Ana adds a deeper layer to candidate evaluation and communication. Whether managing multiple roles, supporting executives, or enhancing candidate experience, she leads with empathy, organisation, and precision.

Work Experience

Apr 2024 – Oct 2024 Technical Recruiter @ Reloading®

Nov 2023 – Apr 2024 IT Talent Acquisition @ Stellaxius

· Maternity Leave Cover

Jan 2022 – Sep 2023 Talent Acquisition Coordinator @ Human2Human

May 2021 – Sep 2023

Talent Acquisition Specialist @ EDP Global Solutions RPO

Feb 2020 - Sep 2023

Human Resources Consultant @ EDP Global Solutions RPO

Jun 2018 – Jun 2019 Human Resources Intern @ EDP

Oct 2016 – May 2017

Psychology Internship @ República Portuguesa - Justiça

Education

ISPA - Instituto Universitário, Lisbon, Portugal Master of Science - MS, Clinical Psychology – (2015 – 2017)

ISPA - Instituto Universitário, Lisbon, Portugal Bachelor of Science - BS, Social Sciences - (2011 - 2015)

Additional Information

- · Employer Branding
- Applicant Tracking Systems

- HR Consulting
- Talent Management Best Practices with SAP SuccessFactors
- Personality and Ability Assessment Training
- Health and Safety Training Course
- Certified Member (CM)
- People Analytics and Evidence-Based Management